Aaaaah!
It's Rob Luffy!
Then it's true.
They came here to kill Vegapunk
just as he feared that they would.
Who the hell invited you pigeon guy?
You get out of here!
This is a government island.
Oh, crap, you're right.
We're the ones who aren't
supposed to be here.
Ah!
Will you focus?
None of that matters!
Come on, Luffy.
We've got to get to the upper level now.
The Straw Hats, huh?
Didn't know this place had a pest problem.
Jewelry Bonnie, too.
But we can't do anything yet, Luchi.
Remember, Straw Hat is an
emperor of the sea now.
We can't fight him without
permission from the top.
He's right.
The four emperors often
have powerful allies.
One little scuffle could lead to a war.
Send a report to the Navy now. Roger.
I'm not sure we can
avoid a fight so easily.
I gotta go, Jinbei. Hold on to you.
Huffy, what's the matter?
What happened?
Wait, I know her.
It's that girl from before.
Chopper, help her, please.
I'm sorry, though.
I think this is more
Frankie's specialty than mine.
This is government business.
You would be wise to stay out of it.
She fed us!
She took care of us when we came
here, and that makes her a friend!
Oh...
Bunchy, Bunchy Notimate, I got one piece!
I can't sleep, and the brain is біль.
And I will fight!
gewalm All Over's is the
adventure of this adventure.
The Straw Hats are on Egghead?
Why, dammit?
See this?
You give people an inch and they
give you nothing but a headache.
You must have figured out that
CP0 was there to kill him.
That's not a good sign.
Yes, sir.
That's likely why they had to
use Espar to teleport inside.
What they did is declare war.
Wish they'd had the common
sense to contact me first.
Those arrogant brats.
If Vegapunk has the Straw Hats on his
side, this could be a real disaster.
Who knows how many good
marines we could lose.
Where's Kizaru?
He's on his way to Egghead right now.
He was already en route, in
service of a different mission.
Tell Luchi to avoid any further
action until backup arrives. Sir!
No matter what happens, we
cannot let him fight Straw Hat!
Intruder alert!
Evacuate immediately!
I repeat, evacuate immediately!
You take Bonnie, I'll take her. Let's go!
Yeah, we need to get her
to Franky right away!
You ready, Luffy?
Go on without me. Woo-hoo!
Oh, my God.
What was that form in your wanted poster?
What, you want to see it?
Do you need to ask?
Ha!
What the hell?
Oh, my God.
I'll be damned.
This should be fun.
Oh,
he he
he
he he!
Hey! Yoo-hoo! Pigeon guy!
Get over here!
Let's fight some more!
Still playing games, even
when your life is on the line?
I'm starting to get annoyed.
Ah, no!
Ah!
Don't get cocky, Straw Hat.
I've gotten stronger just like you have.
All the better to eat prey like you alive.
Wait, something's different.
He definitely didn't
look like that before.
Stop, Luchi!
We don't have authorization for this!
His speed is incredible,
but so is his control.
It's rare that an awakened Snow user
can maintain their state of mind.
What? Oh!
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
He-he-he-he!
It's mine!
Susie! Susie! Susie!
You're out of control!
Please think of the position you're in!
The government will
hunt you down for this!
Shaka!
What happened?
Did the Whitehead Warrior appear?
Oh, my God!
Real Vegapunk!
How the hell did he get up here so fast?
Remarkable!
Tell me more!
I must know everything
about this transformation!
What is that for?
Well, it's new, so we
don't know much either.
But it's a Gum-Gum thing, right?
It's a Devil Fruit encyclopedia.
There is no mention of a Gum-Gum fruit.
This must be something else.
Huh?
Wait, are you saying it's
a different Devil Fruit?
If that's true, then why does
he say Gum-Gum all the time?
Oh, he's so beautiful.
That is a figure from the ancient past,
one with the same form
your captain has now.
A god from the old texts.
A god?
I'm sorry, Luffy?
Stupid and cornered Luffy?
Yes.
The warrior of liberation.
He who plays the fool
and brings smiles to all.
There's no mistaking him.
He is the sun god, Nika!
Nika?
I've never heard of him.
That's no surprise.
The world government erased
his name from history.
But as long as people yearn
for the warrior of liberation,
he will never truly disappear.
For it is desire that brings
forth everything in this world.
Take for example, the devil
fruits and all their power.
You can see it, can't you?
Each Devil Fruit is a possibility
for evolution that someone desires.
I wish I could do this.
I wish I could do that.
All of the powers represent
potential futures of humanity.
But these fantastic possibilities
are not a natural part of this world.
So the mother of nature,
the sea, rejects them.
Therefore, you might say...
Those who have powers live
in different realities.
Realities someone dreamed of.
That is my hypothesis!
Wonder God's existence is irrelevant!
What an interesting
world, wouldn't you say?
Do those idiots know
where they're fighting?
This isn't a playground.
Not for pirates and not for CP0, either.
Why are you bothering me on my day off?
Why did you take so long to answer?
Whatever.
I'm here, aren't I?
So what's the plan, punk?
Cipher Pole is our ally, and the
pirates are the enemy, right?
Do you want me to just
back up CP0 or what?
Quite the opposite, I'm afraid.
CP0 is here to assassinate me,
so I need your help to escape.
Don't get caught up in the details.
Just keep them away.
I can't do that.
Do you know what they do to traitors?
You're right.
My apologies.
But let me ask you this.
Sentomaru?
Can't you do this one teensy favor for me?
The man who saved you from poverty?
All those years ago?
Wow, no pressure, huh?
Is he going to attack us?
Three Seraphim.
I'm not looking forward to this.
Esbear, thin out their numbers.
Esbear, don't move!
We can't beat them. Not like this.
Go, Esbear!
Take out CP Zero!
They're the enemy!
Retreat!
We need a new plan, and fast. No kidding.
So the issue is that Central Moria outranks
the authority chips we're carrying?
That's right.
The system of control is a hierarchy.
If someone whose higher
rank gives an order,
that's the order the Seraphim will follow.
The highest on the authority
chain are the five elders.
The second highest is Dr.
Vegapunk
The third is Saint Moria.
And authority chip holders
like us are the fourth!
No matter what we do, Saint Maru's
commands will always be prioritized.
Then why don't we make a call to the
five elders and have them take control?
It doesn't work that way!
Pacifistas have to receive
their commands directly.
They won't react to a transponder snail,
even if it is the Five Elders Calling.
Then what are we supposed to do?
The Seraphim are valuable
government property.
We can't just destroy them.
Darn it, Lucci!
You really didn't think this through.
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
Woo hoo!
You ready?
Go, go!
Move!
Go!
Time to do this.
First, F-Snake, guide Straw Hat and
his friends to the vacuum rocket.
They need to make it to the frontier dome.
S-Hawk! S-Sharp!
Hold CP0 back!
Chopper, do those children
look familiar to you?
Apart from the Black Wings and the Flames,
they all look like former
warlords of the sea.
You're right.
There's no way that's a coincidence.
The government must have
made clones out of us.
Hey!
Axe Guy!
It's been a while, old buddy.
Tch, Straw Hat.
Current circumstances aside,
you and I are enemies.
And I have a name.
So what?
You're helping Punk escape?
Do I have that right?
Uh-huh.
I like his apple head.
And he asked.
Well, that doesn't exactly
fill me with confidence.
But I suppose you are an emperor now.
Hand pistol.
Black Sky!
That takes care of your commander.
Seraphim, you follow our orders now.
I'm sorry!
I just got to do it, now you're dead!
Idiot.
You didn't distract me.
I saw that it coming.
That was so short.
I'm locked in time.
Hurry up and die.
I can't take control
until you're unconscious.
I'm sure you thought you had a fine strategy
on writing our orders to the Seraphim.
But all you did was put a
nail in your own carpet!
GUMGUM!
GUMGUM! JOHN!
Loochie.
Now's our chance!
Hurry, Luffy!
If we want to save this girl's life,
then we have to get to
Vegapunk's lab immediately!
I mean, it's not like I don't
want to, but, uh... Blah!
I can't stop spinning!
Whoa, you really can't stop spinning!
Somebody call a doctor, quick!
Sorry, I can't stop the winner to grow!
Factory! Hurry!
Is there nothing we can
do to stop these things?
We're losing men to our own weapons.
I shudder to imagine how strong
they'll be once they grow up.
Hey, Vegapunk!
What's wrong?
Tell me the truth.
What is that power?
And what the hell is that
Jinbei thing doing with it?
Guess that looks like the
Swim Swim Fruit to me.
What's the Swim Swim Fruit?
It's his.
My hard-boiled brother from another
mother, Sonar Pink, has that power.
I'd recognize it anywhere.
But it's impossible for there to
be two of the same Devil Fruit,
so that means my bro must have died!
My poor bro!
So you would think.
But he's not dead.
He's just been held in Impel Down.
Hold up.
Does that mean you found a
way to duplicate Devil Fruits?
Well, some Devil Fruits can be copied.
But it only works with Snow types.
The less said about Caesar's
smile experiments, the better.
Yeah, he can go straight to hell.
The smiles offer a high
risk and low success rate.
They only work one time out of ten.
And those who aren't granted power
never stop smiling or laughing.
They can't even mourn for
their lost loved ones.
It's sick. Caesar.
Just hearing his name again
makes me want to blow chunks.
Aberrations such as those notwithstanding.
I have not given up.
If we had enough fun to, and enough time,
we could replicate any
Devil Fruit in the world.
So, I'm not sure if they'll awaken.
I've tried to recreate Lock
powers, but I've had no luck.
And yet, for a Paramecia fruit,
I need only acquire the
bloodline elements of its owner.
Then I can synthesize a special compound!
Which, when administered, confers the
Devil Fruit power to another person.
Observe, that's the fluid you see
flowing through the seraphim's arms.
The green blood.
Hold up!
You made a new can of blood?
L-love?
Beam!
I believe that Seraphic represents the
pinnacle of modern scientific possibility.
Where's the shock go?
Do you know what's that make them?
The strongest form of humanity in history.
Is that why the government
got rid of them?
Why the hell would you even make something
stronger than a warlord, you psychopath?
They're navy weapons killing machines.
Yes.
And sooner or later,
they'll be aiming for us.
Hold on, Sentomaru!
Stay back!
This isn't over yet.
Sentomaru, please stay safe!
Now where did that little
friend of yours run off to?
I don't know.
And he's not my friend!
What a shame.
Guess you're all alone, traitor.
We're out.
Hey! Hey!
You, boy!
Uuh! You, boy!
Ah!
Oh!
Oh! Ahh!
Yes, I'm!
Ah!
Huh?
Hmm?
You?
Who? Huh?
Huh?
Huh? Huh?
Uh? Ah...
Huh... Huh...
Uh...
Ah! Ah!
Hehehehe... Uh! Uh!
Ah!
Uh!
Ha!
Mm-hmm.
Don't stop!
God!
Come on!
Rocky!
When did he get so powerful?
Damn it.
I'm losing consciousness.
Ha-ha-ha!
Follow me, quickly!
I said hurry!
This is no time to be
dragging your feet, you fools!
The vacuum rocket is right there!
Now get on!
Why, thank you!
You know you're much kinder
than the real Hancock.
We owe you one! Much obliged!
What?
Dude, don't be absurd!
I'm just following orders, all right?
Vacuum rocket departing in one minute.
Oh wait, come on, we're out of time!
Hurry up!
What do I do? Attention.
Please take caution while
boarding the rocket. Strike!
Go!
Then take care of punk!
You hear me?
Okay!
Leave it to me!
No!
You're going the wrong way!
Caution.
Doors closing in ten seconds.
We're gonna get him off this island.
No matter what!
I promise.
Doors closing.
Prepare to launch!
Isn't so neat?
It's certainly something, all right.
Where am I?
What happened to Bagel Punks?
Huh?
Where's Pinchin' Guy?
Let me out of here! Whoa!
Who the hell is this?
It's Loopy!
He's just tired!
I'll give you the details later!
How long have I passed out?
Okay, maybe I'll get used to it!
Oh, Gunnar, please shut up!
Easy does it!
You'll shut up too, Grandpa!
Don't get to normal already!
Departing Fabrio base.
Entering Lobby base.
Transit duration 32 seconds.
You have arrived already.
All subsequent rockets are cancelled.
Lobby phase under Loguetown.
Frontier dome security system engaged.
Hostile intruder alert.
All researchers evacuate to the factory
immediately and seal all entry points.
Well, I will say this for the man.
He was a faithful bodyguard to Vegapunk.
Tilt his dying breath.
Such a waste.
Didn't have to end like this, Sentomaru.
Need I remind you, our orders are to
wait for the Navy before making a move.
They can twiddle their
thumbs all they like,
but I won't wait for Vegapunk to escape.
What do they even stand
to gain from killing you?
You're the smartest man in the
world, and you're on their side.
If they do this, it'll
be a huge loss for them.
Well, I think so.
But it appears that the higher-ups
have a different perspective.
I certainly made inventions that have
been beneficial to the world government.
Innovations in navigation
technology using sea brism stones.
Cyborg animal modifications.
Not to mention my research on devil
fruits that's unlocked their secrets,
or my creation of human
weapons with the pacifistas.
And now, I've completed
the Seraphim as well.
Now imagine if you thought I might turn
that frightful intelligence against you.
Fuck what you do!
In that case, there's no choice. Hmm?
I said!
I will not!
For the record, I never planned to revolt.
I still need my research
funding after all.
But the powers that be decided
I was troubling that was that.
Alas, life gives you lemons.
Government tries to kill you for them.
That is not how the expression
goes, and you know it!
Just when I faced this quandary, an
emperor and his crew appeared before me.
Fate brought us together, don't you think?
Hold it!
You mean you want to join our crew?
Welcome aboard, crewmates!
Super! Super!
Which of my babies do
you want to see first?
The Sonny?
General Franky?
What?
So we have to take him?
Well, this sucks.
Don't you worry, Nami!
I'm on bodyguard duty.
Oh my, what a gentleman.
Thank you, I feel much
safer now. Uh, what?
Shut up and unlock these
shitty shoes already!
I wasn't talking to you!
Oh no! Atlas! This is serious!
She's not pooping at all.
Don't worry, we'll save you.
Ready a repair session immediately.
Patient incoming.
Thank you for bringing her in.
You can leave the rest to us.
Of course. Good luck.
Hey, screws for brains.
Where the hell is Vegapunk?
I know he's in here somewhere.
Tell me now.
Barney, stop it.
You need to calm down.
Wait a sec.
Is this his lab?
Wow!
So cool!
Are you seeing this, Bonnie?
That ancient bastard!
I'm gonna make him pay!
Bonnie!
Wait, where are you going?
I told Vegapunk to turn my father
back to normal, and what did he do?
He sipped bugs on me!
I'm going to bury him for this.
I...
don't think the bugs
were his fault, though.
Ugh...
Sonic, wait!
We need to stick together!
Hey, come back!
Our authority chips are
finally back in effect.
The Seraphim follow our orders now.
Who's ready for a little revenge?
I took down one of the satellites.
Including Vegapunk himself,
there are six more.
This might not be easy.
That's assuming we can even get to them.
Trust me, that defense system
is nothing to scoff at.
We'll see how long it
lasts against our forces.
Lock down the island.
Destroy every last ship.
You can find no one escapes.
Egghead on our watch.
The Straw Hats are protecting vagabond.
How nice of them.
Well, I'm sure they'll be a big help.
Too bad they still won't escape.
They're in for one hell
of a surprise, after all.
All right, proceed
according to plan, boys.
Send every last ship we have...
to Egghead Island.
Thank you.